谁会后悔因为今天不帮我建鸭子村
Okay, who would hate to miss the chance of a lifetime
而错过这个千载难逢的机会呢
by not helping me build a duck village today?
这话好绕人啊
That was some tricky wording.
他想先绕晕我们再让我们帮忙
That's how he gets us.
我听懂了 我不会后悔因为不帮你
I got it -- I would not hate to miss
而错过这个千载难逢的机会
the chance of a lifetime by not helping you.
但那只是因为我今天要工作
But only 'cause I have work.
我要上驾驶课
I've got a driving lesson.
有事
Uh, something.
亲爱的 你好几周前就把这些蛋拿回来了
Honey, you found those eggs weeks ago,
到现在都还没孵化
and they still haven't hatched.
你难道不该做好心理准备接受
Should you prepare yourself for the possibility
这些蛋可能是...
that they might be...
鳄鱼蛋吗
Alligators?
-死了 -什么
- Dead. - What?!
你姐姐竟然说出这种话 你信吗
Can you believe your sister?
我信啊 已经死了
Yeah, I do. They're dead.
这件厨房里唯一已经死了的
The only thing that's dead in this kitchen
是你们孩童般的好奇心
is your childlike sense of wonder.
早上好 邓菲们
Morning, Dunphys.
鸭子还没出世哈
Oh, still no ducks, huh?
神奇的生物啊 我刚读了一本这方面的书
Fascinating creatures. I just read a book about them.
是吗
You did?
当然 老妈 迪兰看书的
Yes, mom. Dylan reads.
是我外甥的书
It was my nephew's book.
讲的是一只鸭子和一只企鹅
It was about a duck and a penguin
一起去度假
who go on vacation together.
你可以摸到鸭子的绒毛
You could touch the duck's fuzz.
哔哔[快进音效]
Bloop-bloop!
她想让我快进的时候就会发出这种声音
That's the sound she makes when she wants me to fast-forward.
我懂你
I feel you, money.
克莱尔也会这样对我
Claire does the same thing to me.
我觉得是从我发明那款新牙线开始的
I think it started when I was inventing that new dental floss.
哔哔
Bloop-bloop-bloop-bloop!
这本书上说鸭子从一出生开始
So, the book said ducklings imprint on their mom
就印刻它们的妈妈
as soon as they're born.
它们的脑子特别小 所以就依随着某样东西
Their brains are so small, they just latch on to something
然后牢牢跟着来获取食物
and follow it around as a way to find food.
好吃
Yum.
迪兰 我一会儿要建一个鸭子村
So, Dylan, I'm building a duck village later.
你想帮忙吗
You want to help?
这个问题好绕人
That's some tricky wording on that question.
他想帮忙 但是他还得...
He'd love to, but he's still --
时间到了 快煮毛巾
It's time! Boil some towels!
每次我吃鸡蛋你都要这样吗
Every time I have an egg? Really?
塔克接住
Tucker goes deep!
小心
Watch it.
小卡
Cam!
慕奇有空位吗
Hut, hut, hut! Munch, you open?
没人防他
Oh, he's open!
接球 接到了
Right there! There it is!
我们最近把楼上的房间租给了小卡原来大学里的
We have been renting the upstairs unit to some frat boys
脑残青年[兄弟会成员]
from Cam's old college.
他们来这里看比赛
They're here for some big game
顺便试试能不能上《购物街》节目
and to try and get on "The Price is Right."
但对我而言不幸的是
Unfortunately for me,
这完全激发了小卡"梁山情义"的一面
it has brought out Cam's "Bromosexual" side.
-史诗级的传球啊 弟兄们 -赞
- Epic throw, bro. - Yeah!
其实这是羊绒上的传球
Actually, that is a cashmere throw,
现在上面有脚印了
which now has a footprint on it.
伙计们 来玩啤乓球吧
Dudes, beer pong!
乓 乓 乓
Pong, pong, pong!
啤酒在冰箱里 弟兄们
Beers are in the fridge, bros.
冰箱 冰箱 冰箱 冰箱
Fridge, fridge, fridge, fridge!
-不 等等 弟兄 -怎么了 亲爱的
- No, hang on, bro. - What's up, sweetie?
你终于归位了
Oh, look who's back.
我发现你今天又请你朋友过来了呢
Um, so I see that you invited your friends again today.
是啊 他们是不是很好玩 你看杰斯多可爱
Yeah, aren't they fun? And how cute is Jace?
我们之前拉过手了
We held hands earlier.
其实是掰手腕 但还是算数啊
We were arm wrestling, but it still counts.
我们找到冰箱了
We found the fridge!
哟 你们做到了
Yo, you did!
那个就是杰斯
That's Jace.
到底有多少个杰斯
How many S's in 'Jace'? I heard 12.
我只是想让我们的客人开心些
I'm just trying to make our guests feel comfortable.
好了 来吧
All right, let's do this!
大爸为什么那样子说话
Why is Daddy talking like that?
婊疯矣[街头俚语]
She crazy.
好啦 怎么了啦
Ay, what is it?!
我不对劲的时候你总能看出来
You can always tell when something's wrong.
她叫什么
What is her name?
切尔西 是给我做过
Chelsea, the prettiest barista who's ever served me
双份半咖焦糖玛奇朵撒肉桂粉的
a double-shot half-caff caramel macchiato
最美的咖啡师
with a dusting of cinnamon.
我想搭讪她
I want to talk to her,
但我每次张口的时候 我就傻了
but whenever I do, all I can say is.
可能是因为你点咖啡时把词汇量都用完了
Maybe you used up all your words ordering that coffee.
你为什么这么害怕
Why are you so scared?
能看到你那双美丽的眼睛 听到你甜美声音的女人
Any woman would be so lucky to look into those beautiful eyes
是多么的幸运
and listen to that sweet voice.
-她是如此地... -我的节目开始了
- She's so -- - My show is on!
真美啊
Ay, que linda...
玛瑞拉·莫纳拉斯是我最爱的女演员
Mariela Morales is my favorite actress,
她要用卡梅丽塔·孔特雷拉斯这个假名
and she's staying in a hotel in town
住在城里的一处酒店里
under the fake name Carmelita Contreras.
我要在大厅里等她
I am going to wait for her at the lobby,
我知道我听起来像个跟踪狂
and I know I sound like a stalker,
但是这不一样
but -- but this is very different,
因为我们一见面就会像闺蜜一样
because when we meet, we're going to be best friends.
我仿佛已经能闻到她的发香
I can already smell her hair.
好了 广告时间
Okay, commercials.
所以你应该这样
So, this is what you're going to do.
首先 你要带我去酒店见玛瑞拉
First you're gonna take me to the hotel to meet Mariela.
我要请她今晚来家里吃饭
I'm gonna invite her over for dinner tonight.
她五点要参加一个慈善活动
She has a charity event at 5:00,
但他们不管饭
but they're not serving food.
-跟踪狂 -我跟玛瑞拉在一起的时候
- Stalker. - While I'm with mariela,
你就回去找你的咖啡女孩
you're gonna go back to your coffee girl
你要给她机会让她认识你
and you're gonna give her the chance to get to know you.
你真的觉得我...
You really think I --
广告结束了
Commercial is over.
-又是这个剧吗 -是的
- This show again? - Yes.
我不知道这是什么剧 但我好爱这个角色
I don't know what it is. I love this character so much.
那个老家伙是谁
Who's the old crank?
当然是她老公了
Her husband, of course.
那个戴围巾的是个什么鬼
Who's the disaster with the scarf?
她儿子 佩皮托
Her son, Pepito.
你跟那个人至少还长得像
You at least look like your guy.
-我那个人... -是吗 佩皮托
- My guy -- - Can it, Pepito.
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
你能看得清吗
Can you read that?
-嘎嘎尼科尔森 -太好了
- "Quack Nicholson". - Oh, good.
我花了一早上漆这个迷你鸭子信箱
If I spent the whole morning painting these
结果要是没人能看得清
tiny duck mailboxes and no one could read them,
那我岂不是傻了吗
I'd feel pretty ridiculous.
菲尔 鸭食[邓菲]
Phil, duck feed!
听起来好像我的名字
Hey, that's almost my name.
你是不是该说对不起
Or "I'm sorry"?
你说的没错 对不起 我...
You're right. I'm sorry. I'll, uh --
我一会儿就把它扫干净
I'll sweep that up in a minute.
过来帮我把身上掸干净
Just come over here and help dust me off.
我有个重要会议
I've got an important meeting,
我不能带着满身亚麻籽去上班
And I can't go into the office covered in flaxseed.
这其实是燕麦 毛毛虫以及蟋蟀
It's actually a proprietary blend
按一定比例混合的独家配方
of oats, grub worms, and cricket parts.
-掸干净 -对不起
- And we're dusting. - Yeah, sorry.
你不是在为今天的会议感到紧张吧
Yeah. You're not nervous about the meeting today, are you?
我是很紧张
Yeah, I am.
这是我第一次在我爸和他那自大的设计团队面前
This is the first time I'm pitching closet-design ideas
做有关橱柜设计想法的演讲
to my dad and his pretentious creative team.
你说的是圣诞派对上拄着拐棍的
You mean the young guys with the walking sticks
-那些年轻人吗 -是啊
- at the Christmas party? - Yes.
他们觉得总部里的人比不上他们
They don't think anybody in corporate can do what they do,
可我的想法很好
but my ideas are good.
或者很烂
Or they suck.
我来开门
I've got it!
你的想法肯定很棒 别怀疑自己
I'm sure your ideas are great. Stop doubting.
你越相信自己 他们也会越相信你
The more you believe in yourself, the more they will.
谢谢
Thank you.
学霸好
Hey, nerds.
别介意
Ignore this.
你想让我帮你做的
So, what's this super-fun project
"超级有趣"的项目是什么
you want me to help you with?
我们要建一个鸭村
We are building a duck village.
妈
Um, hey, Mom,
我的驾校教练说今天不能上课了
My driving instructor just canceled on me.
真糟 好吧 我来做你的教练
Oh, shoot, fine. Fine, I'll take you.
真糟 好吧 我坐后座
Oh, shoot, fine. I'll sit in the back.
不 不 你留在这里帮菲尔
No, no, no. You're gonna stay here and help Phil.
我们去见你的表亲们
Let's go meet your cousins.
谢啦 米奇尔舅舅
Well, thanks, Uncle Mitch.
好
Yeah.
你知道卢克路考已经两次没过了吧
You know Luke has failed that driver's test twice now, right?
我今天能选的只有脑残屋 鸭村或者车祸
My options today are frat house, duck village, or car crash.
我觉得我的选择没问题
I'm feeling very comfortable with my decision.
这些灯是干什么的啊
What are you doing with those lights?
我想给这些蛋升温
I'm trying to get some heat on these eggs.
由于和普通商品弄混
Due to a grocery mishap,
它们不幸在冰箱里待了几个小时
they spent about seven minutes in the fridge.
他一个月前发现了这些蛋
So, uh, eggs he found a month ago,
又要给它们建一个鸭村...
building a whole village for them now...
家里一切都还好吧
How's everything at home? Okay?
我们有一些关于这些鸭子是否存活的探讨
There is some debate as to the alive-ness of the ducklings.
但我得说
But I have to say,
与抱着那种信念和乐观的人一起生活
living with that kind of belief and optimism,
真是没法不受影响啊
it just rubs off on you.
我只想...
I am just gonna...
这应该能让我的这些蛋[蛋蛋]保持温暖
This should keep my eggs warm.
你怎么这么安静 我做错什么了吗
You are just so quiet. What am I doing wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
安静会让我紧张
Silence makes me nervous.
说点什么吧
Talk about something.
聊聊你今天过得如何
Tell me about your day.
好吧
Uh, okay.
今天早上 起床的时候
Well, this morning, uh, I woke up
差点被一个橄榄球打断鼻梁
and almost got my nose broken by a football.
我们楼上住了几个脑残青年
We have some frat guys staying upstairs,
小卡经常跟他们一起玩
and Cam hangs out with them a lot.
你不喜欢吗
And you're not okay with that?
我不知道 也许吧
I don't know. I-I guess.
谁会在意
Who cares?
拜托 让我切进去[说给我听听]
Come on, let me in.
好吧 坦白讲
Okay, if I'm being honest,
小卡的行为让我感觉很尴尬
I find Cam's behavior a little embarrassing,
主要是他说的那些"哟"啊"弟兄"啊
You know, with all of his "Yos" and "bros".
省省吧
I mean, calm down.
你一个中年基大叔
You're a middle-aged gay man
就不要边说话边扭屁股了
who punctuates sentences with your hip.
终于切进来[说出来]
Finally.
就是啊 承认这一点感觉真舒服
I know. It feels good to admit it, you know?
走吧[继续说]
Go on.
你知道还有什么很烦人吗
You know what else is really irritating?
他多渴望跟他们在一起
How needy he is with them.
让我进去
Let me in.
怎么了 弟兄
What up, bro?
你们没意识到你们有多吵吗
Do you seriously not know how loud you're being?
邻居全都在抱怨
The neighbors are complaining.
我尊重你们 你们却完全不尊重我
I give you guys respect, and you give me nothing.
我是说 我们...
I mean, we -- we --
骗到你们了
Got you!
什么
What?
你们真该看看你们那样子
You should have seen your faces.
你们一脸 "不是吧
You were like, "What?
我 我们真的很对不起"的表情
W-we -- we really are j-just so sorry!"
-骗到我们了 -这一招不错吧 弟兄们
- You got us. - That was a good one, bro.
你真该跟我们来几杯
You got to do shots with us.
-好吧 -慕奇 去拿野格酒
- Okay. - Munch, get the jaeger.
我们是不是应该拿小纸杯来喝
Yeah, should we serve the potion in cups of dixie?
-或者... -别废话 赶紧去拿吧
- Or the -- - Just get it, dude.
好
Yeah.
我刚想到了一个超屌逼的主意
I just had the sickest idea.
卡罪犯应该加入我们的任务
Caminal should join our mission.
卡罪犯是谁 是我吗
Who's caminal? Am I -- am I caminal?
你们想让我加入你们的任务吗
You want -- you want me to go on a mission?
当然啦 你屌得飞起 老兄
Of course! You're auto-bid, dog.
好吧 任务是什么
Okay, what is this mission?
先喝酒
This first.
为您呈现的是 至高无上的野格酒
Presenting Lord and Lady Jaeger.
闻起来应该是这个味儿吗
Does this smell the way it's supposed to smell, or...
酒不多了 所以我混了一下
We were low, and I had to mix.
为您呈现的是 至高无上的野格-奎沃-韦泽酒
Presenting Lord and Lady Jaeger-Cuervo-Weiser.
小卡 小卡 小卡
Cam! Cam! Cam!
基本想法就是以上这些
So, that's just the rough idea.
如果想要看更多草图
If you want to see more sketches,
可以去我的"橱柜云"账户
just check out my ClosetCloud account.
虽然我只是公司的一员
Um, look, I know I'm just a suit in this company,
但我还是要说 我感到有点失望
But I've got to say, I'm a little underwhelmed.
-我喜欢这想法 -因各位的反应而失望
- I love it. - By the reaction from the rest of you suits.
拜托 我们是一家人
Come on, we're a family. Right?
亲爱的 我们可以去跟乔治·罗斯聊了吗
So, honey, are we all set for our pitch with George Ross
-就在今天下午 -好的 先生
- this afternoon? - Yes, sir.
我之前不是让你别叫我"亲爱的"了吗
What did I tell you about "honey"
-抱歉 -不要在公司里叫
- Sorry. - At the office?
好吧 如果没有其它事情...
Okay, so, if there's nothing else --
其实 如果你们不介意
Actually, um, if -- if you don't mind,
我想展示一下我自己的设计
I'd like to show you some designs of my own.
总部的人现在也会展示新设计了吗
So, corporate is pitching creative ideas now?
我知道我看起来不像那种
I know I don't look like
踩滑板上班的人
I just rode to work on my skateboard.
完了 说到你了
Snap. Look at you.
但对需要专门脱离盒外思考[创新思维]的人群来说
But for people who are paid to think outside the box,
你们却依旧束缚于盒子内部
you people are pretty inside the box
而这盒子正是我们所说的"伟大的衣柜"
when it comes to the box we call the mighty closet.
-关灯 -看来她是玩真的
- Lights. - So I guess we're doing this.
我想称这款衣橱为"大使先生"
I like to call this model the Ambassador.
在我们的皇室复兴系列大获成功之后
After the success of our royal renaissance series,
我在想 挂衣杆为什么不用黄铜杆呢
I thought, "Why not brushed brass for the valet rods?"
已经试过了 开灯
Been done. Lights.
什么 我没太明白
What? I'm, I'm sorry.
五年前就试过了 没什么用
We tried it five years ago. It didn't work.
这种杆子挂不住丝质衣物
Silk shirts slip off the brass.
我才刚开始呢
Okay. Well, I'm just getting started.
关灯
Lights.
这种样板有一个特殊的隐藏式收纳柜
This model features a hidden tilt-out hamper.
-这主意很棒 -谢谢您的赞同
- That's a terrific idea. - I'm glad you think so.
当肯·萨顿在1992年提出这个想法时
Is what Ken Sutton's boss told him
他的老板也是这么认为的
when he pitched it in 1992.
开灯
Lights.
你得精通衣柜发展史啊
You've got to know your history.
真的
Honestly.
我懂了
So, it's --
你想看的是原创衣柜
it's originality you're looking for.
你没搞错吧 花这么大功夫
You're not seriously coming in here,
就给我看田纳西推拉门
pitching me the Tennessee slider.
你就只有这些想法吗
Is that the best you've got?
那就收工吧
Okay, I think we're done here.
老妈
Hey, Mom.
曼尼
Oh, hi, Manny.
你跟那个女孩怎么样了
How did it go with your coffee girl?
我们相处得很棒 真的 我
Really great, actually. Yeah, I--
-你在骗我 -你怎么知道
- You're lying. - How could you tell?
我不知道 你刚刚承认的
I couldn't. You just confessed.
我走向柜台 然后就紧张了
I got up to the counter and panicked.
我买了两张圣诞专辑
I bought two Christmas CDs,
一个根本不吃的松饼 然后走了
a muffin I didn't need, then left.
曼尼 鼓起勇气跟她说话啊
Manny, please just talk to her.
她跟其他人一样啊 你是怎么了
She's like everybody else. What's wrong with you?
妈 我又不是你
Mom, I'm not you.
我走进房间时 周围的人不会转身看我
When I walk into a room, everyone's head doesn't turn.
我说笑话的时候他们也不会捧场笑得特别开心
People don't laugh extra hard at my jokes.
这个世界对你这样的美女总是格外善良
The world is different for people like you.
可是曼尼
Manny, but you --
别说了 我不想说这事
I don't, really don't want to talk about it anymore.
你还是快去吧 不然她就走了
You better hurry. You're gonna miss your chance.
别走开
Okay, stay right here.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
玛瑞拉 玛瑞拉·莫纳拉斯
Mariela! Mariela Morales!
什么事
Si?
你好
Hola!
玛瑞拉
Ma-mariel--
我是怎么了
Ay, what's wrong with me?
玛瑞拉
M-mariel...
有人点了六个大份披萨吗
Somebody order six large pizzas?
谁来付一下钱
Hey, uh, somebody pay the pizza guy.
你们有事吗
Can I help you?
我们是来参加派对的
Uh, yeah. We're here for the party.
我们应该在名单上
We should be on the list.
不好意思
Aw, yeah, my bad.
有那么一秒 我还以为你们是
Yeah, see, for a second, I thought you guys
伊利诺伊来的混球
were just a couple Illinois douches
你们以为我会那么蠢
who thought that I'd be dumb enough
让你们若无其事地走进来
just to let you walk in --
搞什么
What the hell?!
快走
Go!
Go, go!
在约好的地方见
Meet at the rendezvous!
这里是邮局
So, this is the post office,
不然它们就收不到账单[喙]了
cause where else are they gonna get their "bills"?
当然了 你得绕开这个人
Of course, you got to waddle past this guy
才能去做指甲
to get to the nail salon.
街旁边要新开一家混合健身中心
And word on the street is they're putting in a CrossFit next door.
这两个蛋怎么粘粘的
Why are these two eggs sticky?
因为邻居家的狗很不老实
Because the neighbor's dog is a real slobberer,
不过还好我动作快
but lucky, he's not very fast.
我老师告诉我们 说一个人是怪胎是不对的
My teacher says that there's no such thing as weird,
他们只是不一样而已
just different.
你从哪冒出来这个想法的 不过说得很对
That's a lovely random thought.
我画了好几种鸭金汉宫的修建草图
I drew up plans for a Duckingham Palace,
不过我找不到图纸了
but I can't find them,
看来我们只能现场发挥[翅膀]了
so I guess we'll just have to "wing" it.
那是什么东西
What the heck is that?
是能让小鸭子觉得安全的鸭叫声
Oh, it's a duck call to make the ducklings feel safe.
我是不是该找个真正的大人过来
Should there be another adult present?
不用
No.
不过这里应该有个小孩
But there should be a kid present.
你就是那个小孩
That kid is you.
你以后翻白眼的日子还多着呢
You've got your whole life to roll your eyes.
今天我们不只是建造一个鸭子村而已
Today isn't just about building a duck village.
更是要让你学会微笑
It's about building your smile.
别抗拒
Don't fight it.
终于笑了
There it is.
正如你看到的
As you can see,
我们的鸭村港口有一座正在亮灯的灯塔
our little duck harbor has a working lighthouse.
等等 他刚才说了什么
Wait a second, what in the world did he just say?
一座亮灯的灯塔 没错 灯亮着呢
A working lighthouse? Yes, it is working.
很棒对吧
Pretty cool, huh?
别激动 莉莉
Easy, easy, Lily.
忘记掉你听过的一切关于蛋的传闻
Forget everything you've ever heard about eggs.
它们其实很易碎
They're actually quite delicate.
你得很小心 不好
You've got to be very care-- son of a -- aah!
完蛋了
Oh, no!
好烫
Hot!
看
Look.
有蛋叛逃了
We've got a runner!
不
No!
太好了 还跟新的一样
Hey, good as new.
婊疯矣
She crazy.
他让我在自己家觉得像个外人...
He makes me feel like an outsider in my own home, and...
现在这么一说 我突然想起来
Now that I think about it,
自从我们把楼上的公寓租出去后...
ever since we started renting that upstairs apartment...
我们真的要绕远路[扯太远]吗
Do we want to take this detour?
不 这跟我接下来要说的有关
No, it's relevant. Stay with me.
不仅仅是那些脑残青年的问题
It's not just the frat boys. No.
他对所有的租客都这样
He's this way with all of our guests.
小卡换床单
Cam doesn't change the sheets
都不如他换性格换得勤
as much as he changes his personality.
好了 女士们
All right, ladies.
我们已经准备好了热茶
We got some steaming-hot tea,
以及新鲜出炉的饼干
some popping-hot biscuits.
那么现在 让我们来好好唠一唠
Now, let's have a little sizzling-hot gossip.
-别进去 -别啊
- Do not go in there! - Don't!
不要开 我的天
Do not open -- oh, my god!
不要 姑娘 不要再回去
No! Girl, do not go back in there!
我就是觉得小卡做得太过了
I just think Cam tries too hard.
就好像他在求着别人喜欢他一样
It's like he's begging to be liked.
等等 这是条单行道[光是一个人的错]吗
Wait, is this a one-way street?
这个问题问得好
Oh, that's a fair question.
我猜我还是应该试着努力跟人相处
I don't -- I guess I could make more of an effort with people.
我只是
I just --
根本就不擅长这些
It doesn't exactly come naturally to me.
-小卡 -小卡
- Oh, Cam! - Cam!
就连对着两个红发律师我也没啥可说
I couldn't even find anything to say to two red-headed lawyers.
-我找不到路了[没听明白] -抱歉
- I'm lost. - I know.
我扯远了
I'm all over the place.
也许我只是在嫉妒
I think that I'm just maybe jealous
他能跟所有人打成一片
that he can hit it off with anybody.
但我不能因为他人见人爱就生他气
But I can't be mad at him for being likable.
毕竟这也是我爱上他的原因之一
I mean, that's one of the reasons I fell in love with him.
是小卡吗
Cam?
不然你以为我在说谁
Who else would I be talking about?
不是 那个牵着山羊的披萨外卖哥
No, the pizza guy with the goat
看着很像小卡叔叔
looks like Uncle Cam.
好吧 这肯定又是出了什么状况
Okay, I feel like there's a story here.
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
我不想说话
I don't want to talk about it.
好 看在我们"夫夫"一场的份上
Okay, for the sake of our marriage,
我猜这肯定跟那群脑残青年有关
I'm gonna assume that this is frat-related.
那不是我送你的皮带吗
Oh, look -- the belt I got you.
好了 靠边停一下
Okay, pull over.
小卡 你能不能先停一下
Cam, could you just stop for a second?
拜托 停一下嘛
Come on, stop.
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
抱歉在过去几周 我一直对你翻白眼
For the past few weeks, I've been rolling my eyes at you,
觉得你病态地
thinking that you had this pathological need
想要得到所有人的喜爱
to be liked by everyone,
但是我真是大错特错
but I couldn't have been more wrong.
你是天生招人喜欢
All right? People are just drawn to you.
不 我的确是病态地想要被喜欢
No, I do have a pathological need to be liked.
-我就知道 -这是个玩过火的白痴恶作剧
- I knew it. - This is a stupid prank gone wrong,
而我 我也和那群哥们儿走散了
and I've -- I'm separated from the guys.
为了让他们喜欢我 我甚至偷了一只山羊
I wanted them to like me so much I stole a goat.
我成了偷羊贼了 米奇尔
I'm a rustler, Mitchell.
一个十恶不赦的偷羊贼
I'm a filthy rustler.
在我看来并没有这么糟
Okay, well, that seems worse to you than it does to me.
对每一届房客我都是这德行
I do it with all of our guests.
我改变了自我
I change who I am
就为了让他们能更喜欢我
so they'll like me more.
-这样好累 -那就别再继续了
- It's exhausting. - Well, then, stop.
因为你本来的样子已经足够招人喜欢
Because you're likable enough just being you.
我知道
I know.
我讨厌自己有这种不安全的感觉
And this insecurity is a part of me that I do not love.
-卡罪犯 -弟兄们好啊
- Caminal! - What's up, my brothers?!
-小卡 -我到底是怎么了
- Cam. - What is wrong with me?
快上车 我们还要涂山羊呢
Get in -- we got a goat to paint!
不 听着 各位
No, you know what, guys?
这样不对
This isn't right.
我不是这样的人
This is not who I am.
所以我要把山羊还回去
So I'm gonna take the goat back,
如果你们是真朋友 你们会理解我
and if you were ever truly my friend, you'll understand.
你们俩逊爆了
You both suck!
你们才逊
You suck.
好了 来吧
All right, come on.
我把她放后座上吧
Okay, I'll -- I'll put her in back,
别担心 她很温顺的
and, um, don't worry -- she's really friendly.
我才不怕小羊羊呢
I ain't afraid of no goats.
行 把合同发过来吧
Okay, send me the contracts.
我从来都抗拒不了高颜值的脸蛋
I never could resist a pretty face.
别贫了 乔治 我可已经结婚了
Stop it, George. I'm married.
我要去趟洗手间
I'm gonna run to the men's room.
你还好吗 一言不发的
So, everything all right? You've barely said a word.
反正你不需要我帮忙
Well, it's not like you needed my help,
而且我今天出的糗已经够多了
and I think I embarrassed myself enough for one day.
听着 我以前可能对你太苛刻了
Look, I might have been too hard on you before.
我只是太厌倦
I'm just tired of everyone
所有人不停地拿衣柜点子轰炸我
always pitching me their closet ideas.
如果每听一次"下一个最赞衣柜"的点子
If I had a nickel for every time someone came to me
我都能收到一枚硬币的话
with "the next great closet",
我都能把它们塞满这个珀耳塞斯系列大衣柜了
I'd have a Pegasus series split-level walk-in full of nickels.
但是老爸 我入了这一行
But, Dad, I'm in the biz.
早该知道那些都是老掉牙的设计方案
I should have known that those are old design ideas.
没有人能一蹴而就
No one nails it on the first try.
我曾经设计过一款蚌壳式鞋盒
Hell, I once pitched a clamshell shoe container
上面还有活动铰链呢
with a living hinge.
-不是吧 -我那会儿太嫩了
- No. - I was young.
别放弃
Keep with it.
你一定会成功的
You'll get there eventually.
谢谢你
Thanks.
都吃好了吗
We all set?
我去买单
Let me settle up.
谢谢你 老爸
Thanks, Dad.
午餐还不错吧
Pretty exciting lunch, huh?
沙拉还是照旧的凯撒沙拉
The same caesar salad,
衣柜也还是我年年订的那批衣柜
the same closets I order every year.
没错 但是你也满意吧
Yeah, but you're happy with them, right?
不过是衣柜而已
They're closets.
如果你想开阔一下眼界
I-if you're ever looking to expand your horizons a little,
我也有一些比较新颖别致的设计想法
I have some design ideas that are fresh of the drawing board.
很对不起 我的天
I'm sorry. Oh, gosh.
这些是我老公的鸟食
That's my husband's birdseed.
我想给你看看这个设计
I'd love to give you a look-see here.
我来收拾这摊
I'll take care of this.
老天
Heavens.
鸭金汉宫
"Duckingham palace"?
错了 错了 对不起
Oh, no, no. No, no, sorry.
不是这些
Those are the wrong ones.
不是这些方案
Um, wrong plans.
我还有别的方案 特别棒
I've got other ones, and they're -- they're super.
老天啊
oh, gosh.
天哪 它在我头上是吧
Oh, my god. What -- it's -- it's on my head, right?
它在我头上
It's on my head. Okay.
-天 它在我头上 -我的天
- God. Okay. I know it's in here. It's in here. - Oh, my god.
好了 快走开
Okay. Okay.
跑到我衬衫里了
Oh, it's in my shirt.
-我不过走开了三十秒 -老爸 救我
- I was gone for 30 seconds. - Dad, Dad!
也太久了吧
Well, that was forever.
太糗了
I'm so embarrassed.
我从来没那么紧张过
I've never freaked out like that.
很差劲吗
How bad was it?
也就...
I mean...
很抱歉我在你不敢跟切尔西说话这件事
I'm so sorry that I gave you such a hard time
给你施了那么大压力
about not talking to Chelsea.
其实 你算是帮了我的忙
Actually, you kind of helped me out.
为什么
How?
看见你如此反常
Seeing you fall apart like that...
结结巴巴 手足无措地说个不停
stutter, twitch, and babble --
够了 哔哔
Okay, bloop-bloop.
你是这世上最自信的女人
You're the most confident woman in the world,
如果像你这样的人也会像常人一样气馁
and if someone like you can be human,
那我在姑娘面前畏首畏尾也不会觉得难受了
then I don't have to feel bad about chickening out with girls.
你知道谁也是常人吗 切尔西
You know who else is human? Chelsea.
所以你又为什么要怕她呢
So why do you feel so intimidated by her?
去吧 去找她
Go. Go over there.
没时间了
There's no time.
周六她五点就下班了
She gets off at 5:00 on saturday
这样才赶得及拿完干洗的衣服
so that she can pick up her dry cleaning
去上六点的瑜伽课
and make 6:00 yoga.
跟踪狂
Stalker.
打电话给她
Call her.
真的吗
Really?
是的 你可以的
Yes. You can do it.
好吧
Okay.
切尔西你好
Hi, Chelsea?
我刚到店里去过 穿着一件绿色夹克
I was in earlier, wearing the green jacket
比被自己剧本逗笑那人还吵[俗丽]
that's louder than that guy laughing at his own screenplay?
她被逗笑了
She's laughing!
我希望有时间可以跟你一起喝杯咖啡
I would like to take you out for coffee sometime,
也许去一个不用你来冲咖啡的地方
maybe at a place you don't have to make it?
好极了 好的 明天见
Great. O-okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
回见
Bye.
她同意了
She said yes.
她当然会同意
Of course she did.
我真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
看见了吧 这才是个自信的人会做的事
You see, that's what it is to be a confident person.
这些都是由你的母亲遗传给你的
And you got all of it from your mother.
玛...
Mam -- ay!
她叫什么来着
Ay, what's her name?!
什么型号的管子
What size tubing would I need
能让三只小鸭子滑过去
for three ducklings to slide through?
钱不是问题 你去哪里
Cost is no ob-- where are you going?
去后面找一找吗 非常感谢
To the back to check on it? Thank you so much!
看哪 你像个真正的孩子一样在玩石头
Well, look at you playing with rocks just like a real kid.
没错
Yep.
我希望那些蛋没事
Oh, I hope those eggs are doing okay.
把它们自己留在家我很过意不去
I feel bad leaving them alone.
也许那样会更安全
Probably safer that way.
我知道别人都觉得我疯了
I know people think I'm crazy.
我觉得相信别人都不相信的事特别有意思
It's just more fun believing even when no one else does.
谁都可以成为怀疑论者
Anyone can be a doubter.
我跟你说过怎么弄到它们的吗
Did I ever tell you how I got them?
没有 不过...
No, but I, uh...
它们被遗弃在某人的后院 可怜的小东西
I found them abandoned in someone's yard, the poor things.
没有母亲
No mother.
没有人照顾它们
No one to take care of them.
它们是孤儿吗
So, they're orphans?
它们的母亲去哪了
Where did their mother go?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只知道它们现在只有我了
I know I'm all they have now.
-喂 -喂 亲爱的
- Hello. - Hey, honey.
-能帮我个小忙吗 -好
- Can I ask you a tiny little favor? - Okay.
能把那些蛋转九十度吗 顺时针转
Can you rotate the eggs 90 degrees, clockwise?
不 菲尔 我不能
No, Phil, I can't. I can't.
我累死了 而且我满身是汗
I am tired, and I am sweaty,
尽管我这一整天都试图像你一样保持乐观
and as much as I have tried to stay positive like you all day,
但是我觉得有时候还是应该面对现实
I think sometimes we need to just face certain facts
比如总部的人不会有创造性
like corporate people are not creative,
比如鸭蛋一个月孵不出来也许就永远也不行了
and ducks that haven't hatched in a month might never.
把蛋转一下不就得了 老姑
Just turn the eggs, lady!
说真的
You know what?
我今天受够鸟类的气了
Kind of done with birds for the day.
天哪 菲尔
Oh, my god, Phil.
-好像孵化出来了 -等等 什么
- I think it's hatching. - Wait, what?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我该 该做什么
What -- what do I do?
好 保持冷静
Okay, uh, stay calm.
我会教你分娩
I-I'll talk you through the labor.
要生了 莉莉
They're coming, Lily!
好吧 克莱尔 告诉你看到什么了
Okay, Claire -- tell me what you see!
天哪 我好像看到鸭嘴了
Oh, God. I think I see a beak.
好消息是不是脚先出 可以顺产
Well, the good news is we're not breach.
它们看起来像是在努力破壳而出
It looks like it's struggling to break through.
如果你担心会吓到到它
Okay, if you are concerned about traumatizing him,
穿上去年万圣节我们装扮成麦片代言卡通人物
strap on that toucan beak I wore last Halloween
我的那套犀鸟服 帮它们把壳啄开
when we dressed as froot loops and start pecking.
我还是用叉子吧
I'm using a fork.
手别抖 克莱尔 拜托
Steady hands, Claire, please.
我见过你玩"手术"
I've seen you play "Operation".
孵出来了
Oh, it's hatched!
太可爱了
It's so cute.
Oh, it's so cute!
不敢相信我居然错过了
I can't believe I'm missing this!
快让开
Hey, buddy!
对外要宣称我当时在场
We're telling people I was there!
我觉得另一只也要孵化了
I think another one's hatching.
什么 对不起 莉莉
What?! I'm sorry, Lily.
飞跃减速带 三 二...
Speed bump in three, two...
天哪 三只都出来了
Oh, my god, all three?!
太棒了
That's amazing!
-莉莉 拍张照 -好
- Lily, take a picture! - Yep.
好了
Here.
小家伙
Hi, buddy.
准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
一 二
One, two --
稍等
Hold up, hold up.
它进我衣服里了
He's in my shirt.
鸟怎么总爱往我衣服里钻
Another bird in my shirt.
出来了
Got it.
我要去睡了 晚安 宝贝
I'm going to bed. Good night, sweetie.
晚安 等等
Good night. Wait. You know what?
我刚才在想
I was just thinking,
如果那些鸭蛋都能孵出小鸭...
if those duck eggs were still viable...
也许我们应该去找找
Maybe we should find out if you've got
看你那还有没有一两只蛋[卵]也能孵化出来
one or two fighters left in there, too.
不 免了吧
No, thank you.
我受够了有小东西在家里跑来跑去的了
I'm done with little ones running around the house.
别跟着
Stay.
我说了 别跟着
Oh, I said stay.
那些鸭子把克莱尔当成妈妈了
The ducks imprinted on Claire.
没什么大不了的
It's n-not a big deal.
拜托 伙计们
Come on, guys.
她都说了 别跟着
She said stay!
拜托
Come on.